# Alexandra Bryant

5006 Nolda St., Houston, TX 77007 ■ 832-715-1509 ■ BryantAlexandra@ymail.com

#### **OBJECTIVE**

Seeking the opportunity to grow, learn, and contribute with a dynamic professional software engineering team.

#### **SUMMARY**

Currently a Computer Science student at University of Houston, with some experience self-teaching web development and app development, hoping to gain perspective on a variety of types of software building in an agile team environment. Significant experience with C++, Java, and some experience with Swift, C#, JQuery, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and Ruby on Rails.

## **EDUCATION**

Baylor University, Waco, TX

August 2011 – December 2014

University of Houston, Houston, TX

July 2015 – Present

Bachelor's of Science, Computer Science: GPA: 3.0

#### WORK HISTORY

#### Etsy Entrepreneur, Houston, TX

August 2012 – August 2015

From custom design to shipping, operated an internet retail store that offered unique crochet products using a self-taught wire technique. This technique offered malleability to crochet structures that would otherwise lose shape. This business provided a flexible schedule and offered an outlet for creativity and design.

#### Key Results:

- Managed operations of internet retail store fulfilling over seventy custom orders
- Sole responsibility for marketing, product creation, and logistics
- Planned price, cost, advertising, and supplies to counterbalance supply/demand with school schedule
  - **o** Increased retail price to increase/decrease demand in accordance with free-time
- Incorporated mathematical modeling to create unique wire embedded crochet design offering high pliability
- Work-In-Progress: Designing and developing crochet modeling software for use in custom pattern creation

# Torchy's Taco's Waitress, Waco, TX

August 2014 – May 2015

Primary roles were waitressing and cashiering, also filled in for cooks, cleaning staff, and bartenders.

#### Key Results:

- Adapted to different roles as needed under pressure at the busiest Torchy's establishment in the chain
- Maintained positive attitude under prolonged stress and helped foster a good team atmosphere
- Increased business at the bar by changing morning logistics allowing for artful chalkboard signs to be made

# Office Depot, Waco, TX

August 2013 – August 2014

Sole staff of the Copy/Print department. Learned to efficiently use many different types of hardware and software to fulfill customers' needs.

## Key Results:

Debugged hardware and software issues on a wide variety of machines in a timely manner.

## **Personal Projects**

- GitHub: <a href="https://github.com/alexxbryant">https://github.com/alexxbryant</a>
- SteamVR Tutorial Blog: <a href="https://steamvrtutorialssite.wordpress.com/">https://steamvrtutorialssite.wordpress.com/</a>